A Guide to the Arena Stage Dramaturgical Files, 1950-2000
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Arena Stage Dramaturgical files 1950-2000
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Arena 0016
91 boxes comprising 30 cubic feet (45 linear feet)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Donated by the Arena Stage in the fall of 2000
Historical Information
Arena Stage was an early leader in the resident theater movement. One of the first not-for-profit theaters in the United States as well as a pioneer of the regional theater movement the Arena Stage was the first regional theater to transfer a production to Broadway, the first invited by the U.S. State Department to tour behind the Iron Curtain and the first to receive a Tony Award. Co-founded in 1950 by Edward Mangum a teacher from the George Washington University, and Zelda Fichandler one of his students, Arena Stage was opened in Washington D.C. to fill the void left by the closing of the National Theater in 1948. Deriving it's name from the idea of "theater in the round," Arena Stage became one of the first resident theaters in the United States, beginning with a company of only eight actors. Today, Arena performs to over 250,000 patrons during a September to June season and employs nearly 200 theater professionals and craft persons, who are responsible for all the costumes and scenery seen on stage. Many now- famous actors took part in Arena Stage productions during the early part of their careers. Some of them include Robert Prosky, Morgan Freeman, Dianne Weist, James Earl Jones, Kevin Kline, Christopher Guest, Yeardly Smith and Samuel L. Jackson. Donated to George Mason University in fall of 2000, the Arena Stage Collection contains materials spanning the theater's 50 year history including production notebooks, photographs, playbills, scrapbooks, scripts and handwritten correspondence and other production materials.
Scope and Content
Collection contains production information for select Arena Stage productions (1950s to 2000) including scripts, research and study guides, reviews and misc. production notes and information.
Arrangement
By production title
Contents List
- The Arena Stage Dramaturgical Files
  - "Common Ground" workshop, Nov. - Dec. 1992 (Box Box 1)
  - "Common Ground" cont. (Box Box 1)
  - "Common Ground" cont. (Box Box 1)
  - "Common Ground" cont. (Box Box 2)
  - "Common Ground" cont. (Box Box 2)
  - "Common Ground" post-workshop text, 12/92 (Box Box 2)
  - "Common Ground" script adapted by Bill Cain (Box Box 2)
  - "Common Ground" notes (Box Box 2)
  - "Common Ground" script (Box Box 2)
  - "Summer and Smoke", acting script (Box Box 3)
  - Reviews "Summer and Smoke" (Box Box 3)
  - visual images of the south (Box Box 3)
  - critical essay of Tennessee Williams (Box Box 3)
  - information on angels (Box Box 3)
  - Southern History (Box Box 3)
  - references within the play (Box Box 3)
  - "eccentricities of a nightingale", script (Box Box 3)
  - additional background information (Box Box 3)
  - Cheryl West, playwright, bio (Box Box 4)
  - "Jar the Floor", by Cheryl West (Box Box 4)
  - "Jar the Floor" misc. information (Box Box 4)
  - Melanie Klein, works, bio, misc. materials (Box Box 4)
  - "School for Wives" Moliere, 1991-1992 and misc. materials (Box Box 5)
  - Yerma, misc. materials (Box Box 5)
  - "The Way of the World" script (Box Box 6)
  - "The Way of the World" Script (Box Box 6)
  - "The Way of the World", script, notes, background material (Box Box 6)
  - "The Way of the World" research and background (Box Box 6)
  - sex research (Box Box 6)
  - "The Way of the World"background and research info (Box Box 6)
  - "Of Thee I Sing" script, background info (Box Box 7)
  - "Of Thee I Sing" background info (Box Box 7)
  - Otis research (Box Box 7)
  - "Of Thee I Sing", script (Box Box 7)
  - "Of Thee I Sing", "b" script (Box Box 7)
  - "Of Thee I Sing" - original text (Box Box 7)
  - "Of Thee I Sing", Script (Box Box 7)
  - "Let'em Eat Cake", script (Box Box 8)
  - "Of Thee I Sing", script and background info (Box Box 8)
  - "Kiss of the Spider Women", Script and background information/research (Box Box 9)
  - "The Visit" script and background info (Box Box 10)
  - "The Visit", newsletter and program (Box Box 10)
  - "The Visit", script/background info (Box Box 10)
  - "Mrs. Klein", script (Box Box 11)
  - "Mrs. Klein" world and London map and an article (Box Box 11)
  - background info (Box Box 11)
  - "Vivisections from a Blown Mind" background research (Box Box 12)
  - "Vivisections from a Blown Mind", script (2) (Box Box 12)
  - "Vivisection from the Blown Mind", script (Box Box 12)
  - "Vivisections from the Blown Mind" act I (Box Box 12)
  - "Vivisection from the Blown Mind", old act I (Box Box 12)
  - "Trinidad Sister", script, background info/research (Box Box 13)
  - "Trinidad Sisters", script (4) (Box Box 13)
  - "The Father", press release and misc. info (Box Box 14)
  - "The Father", reference material (Box Box 14)
  - correspondence with the Swedish Embassy (Box Box 14)
  - "The Stronger" script and background info (Box Box 14)
  - biographical information for August Strindberg, playwright (Box Box 14)
  - "reviews" publication Winter 1992 (Box Box 14)
  - "The Stronger" research materials (Box Box 14)
  - "The Stronger", images, research, script and notes (Box Box 14)
  - ART News, January 1992 (Box Box 14)
  - criticisms of August Strindberg (Box Box 14)
  - "Arcadia" photos and slides of dress rehearsal (Box Box 15)
  - reviews of "Arcadia" (Box Box 15)
  - study guide materials to "Arcadia" - fall 1996 (Box Box 15)
  - "Arcadia" script and misc. production materials (Box Box 15)
  - "Arcadia" script (Box Box 15)
  - "The Miser", reviews, bio of Moliere and period history (Box Box 16)
  - "The Miser", criticism, 80's history, visual sets, adaptation notes (Box Box 16)
  - "It Ain't Nothin' But the Blues", background information on the blues (Box Box 16)
  - "Ghosts", performance guide and research material (Box Box 17)
  - "Ghosts", script w/notes (Box Box 17)
  - "Voir Dire", visual aids (Box Box 17)
  - "Voir Dire", script, background info/research (Box Box 17)
  - "Candide", background and research book for actors (Box Box 18)
  - :Candide", The Music Theater Study Guide (Box Box 18)
  - "Candide", reviews (Box Box 18)
  - "Candide", post show cheat sheet (Box Box 18)
  - "Dance of Death", synopsis, production meeting notes, bio info for August Strindberg (Box Box 18)
  - "Dance of Death", production book, part I (Box Box 18)
  - "Blithe Spirit", production book, part II (Box Box 18)
  - "Sunday in the Park with George", misc. production materials (Box Box 19)
  - "Sunday in the park with George", research and background information (Box Box 19)
  - "Molly Sweeny", production book (Box Box 19)
  - "Dance of Death", script (Box Box 19)
  - "blithe Spirit", production book (Box Box 20)
  - "The Front Page", background/research materials (Box Box 20)
  - "The Hurricane", articles and research (Box Box 20)
  - "The Hurricane", production book (Box Box 20)
  - "The Hurricane", reviews (Box Box 20)
  - "The Hurricane", study guide (Box Box 20)
  - "Conquest of the South Pole" research material (Box Box 21)
  - "Conquest of the South pole", script (Box Box 21)
  - "Juno and the Paycock", research (Box Box 21)
  - "Juno and the Paycock", reviews and musical score (Box Box 21)
  - "Fences", articles and research (Box Box 21)
  - "Playboy of the West Indies", playbills, articles, misc. materials (Box Box 21)
  - "Blithe Spirit", printed pieces (Box Box 21)
  - "Blithe Spirit", reviews (Box Box 21)
  - "Blithe Spirit",background materials (Box Box 21)
  - "Blithe Spirit", background reading (Box Box 21)
  - "Blithe Spirits", background and research materials (Box Box 22)
  - "Blithe Spirit", script (Box Box 22)
  - "Blithe Spirit", VHS tape of the 1945 version directed by David Lean (Box Box 22)
  - "On the Town", printed pieces, reviews, articles etc. (Box Box 22)
  - "On the Town", script (Box Box 22)
  - "The Man Who Came to Dinner", reviews, printed pieces, articles (Box Box 23)
  - "The Man Who Came to Dinner", printed pieces, study guide, research, reviews (Box Box 23)
  - "The Man Who Came to Dinner", study guide, reviews, research materials (Box Box 23)
  - "The Man Who Came to Dinner", reviews, study guide, background material (Box Box 23)
  - "Lie of the Wind", articles, reviews, background materials (Box Box 23)
  - "Lie of the Mind", background articles (Box Box 23)
  - "She Stoops to Conquer", background material (Box Box 23)
  - "Nothing Sacred", background materials (Box Box 24)
  - "Pygmalion", background readings (Box Box 24)
  - background material for "Born Guilty" (Box Box 24)
  - "Our Town", background material (Box Box 24)
  - "Blood Knot", script (Box Box 24)
  - "Blues for an Alabama Sky", script and background materials (Box Box 25)
  - "Conquest of the South Pole", background materials, including a book of photographs by Amundsen (Box Box 25)
  - "Conquest of the South Pole", research materials (Box Box 25)
  - "Conquest of the South Pole", background materials (Box Box 25)
  - "Ghosts", script (2) (Box Box 25)
  - "The Art of Thornton Wilder", by Malcolm Goldstein (Box Box 26)
  - "Some Notes on Theater", from Wilder (Box Box 26)
  - "Our Town", acting script (Box Box 26)
  - "Our Town", background materials (Box Box 26)
  - "Our Town", research materials (Box Box 26)
  - "Our Town", bound scripts 1938, 1965 (Box Box 26)
  - "Dance of Death", study guide (Box Box 27)
  - Strindberg articles (Box Box 27)
  - Dance of Death Reviews (Box Box 27)
  - "Dance of Death", script (2) (Box Box 27)
  - "The Swan", script (Box Box 27)
  - "Macbeth", adapted script (Box Box 27)
  - "Front Page", original script (Box Box 27)
  - "Voices in the Threshold", script (Box Box 27)
  - "Voices at the Threshold", production materials (Box Box 27)
  - "Voices in the Threshold", research materials (Box Box 27)
  - "Voices in the Threshold", script (2) (Box Box 27)
  - Script (3 drafts): "The Miser" by Moliere, 1996-1997 (Box Box 28)
  - Reviews: "The Miser" by Moliere, 1996-1997 (Box Box 28)
  - Research: "The Miser" by Moliere, 1996-1997 (Box Box 28)
  - video clip research for "The Miser" by Moliere, 1996-1997 (Box Box 4)
  - contract for "The Odyssey", by Derek Walcott, May 1994 (Box Box 29)
  - Arena Stage Public Humanities Project (NEH), Final Performance Report, 1992-1995 (Box Box 29)
  - information on "The Arena Stage Public Humanities Project", 1993 (Box Box 29)
  - NEH budget updates, August 1993 (Box Box 29)
  - Misc. Playquest information (Box Box 29)
  - Misc. Playquest info (Box Box 29)
  - Playquest contracts, 1993 (Box Box 29)
  - Season planning 1996-1997 (Box Box 29)
  - Play Lab budgets etc., 1984-1985 (Box Box 29)
  - Misc. Play Lab info: 1985-1986 (Box Box 29)
  - Play Lab season 1984, misc. (Box Box 29)
  - 1984 Play Lab Season budget (Box Box 29)
  - 1984-1985 Play Lab: in-house reading (Box Box 29)
  - Millennium Voices; 1996 (Box Box 29)
  - Correspondence: Commissions for the 1992-1993 season (Box Box 29)
  - video research for "The Miser" by Moliere, 1996 (Box Box 29)
  - Contract for "The Miser", by Moliere 1995 (Box Box 29)
  - Contract for "Blue for an Alabama Sky", 1996 (Box Box 29)
  - contract for "Voir Dire", 1996 (Box Box 29)
  - "Waiting Room" opening party (Box Box 29)
  - Contract for "The Waiting Room", 1995 (Box Box 29)
  - Contract for "Dance of Death", 1996 (Box Box 29)
  - Study Guide for "Of Thee I Sing", 1992 (Box Box 30)
  - study guide for "A Wonderful Life" and "The Time of Your Life" (Box Box 30)
  - study guide for "The School for Wives", "A Doll House" and "Trinidad Sisters" (Box Box 30)
  - Study guide for "The Brothers Karamazov (Box Box 30)
  - study guide for "Skin of our Teeth" (Box Box 30)
  - study guide for "Blood Knot" (Box Box 30)
  - study guide for "Its the Truth (If you think it is)" (Box Box 30)
  - study guide for "Summer and Smoke" (Box Box 30)
  - study guide for "African Company" (Box Box 30)
  - study guide for "Way of the World" (Box Box 30)
  - script and background information for "A Doll House" (Box Box 30)
  - script and background info for "Stand up Tragedy" (Box Box 30)
  - "I am a Man", symposium details, 1994-1995 season (Box Box 31)
  - contract for "I am a Man" (Box Box 31)
  - synopses of plays, 1993-1994 season (Box Box 31)
  - study guides, 1991-1992 season (Box Box 31)
  - study guide comparisons from other theaters (Box Box 31)
  - study guides, 1989-1990 season (Box Box 31)
  - study guides for "Our Town" and "A Midsummer Night's Dream" (Box Box 31)
  - study guides for the Fall 1990 season (Box Box 31)
  - misc. study guides (Box Box 31)
  - script, reviews and background research for "Merrily We Roll Along" (Box Box 32)
  - script, reviews and background info for "A Midsummer Night's Dream" (Box Box 32)
  - script, reviews and info for "The Glass Menagerie" (Box Box 32)
  - reviews for the Checkmate and Cleveland theaters (Box Box 32)
  - scripts, actors packets and research for "Blue", 1999-2000 season (Box Box 33)
  - "Guys and Dolls" dramaturgy, 1999-2000 (Box Box 34)
  - "Guys and Dolls" reviews and background info (Box Box 34)
  - "Guys and Dolls" research (Box Box 34)
  - "Guys and Dolls" background info (Box Box 34)
  - Guys and Dolls, scripts (Box Box 34)
  - reviews and misc. info for "Guys and Dolls" (Box Box 34)
  - "The Soul Saver" (Box Box 34)
  - "Hot 'N' Throbbing", play bills, 1999-2000 (Box Box 35)
  - "Hot 'N' Throbbing", background research and reviews (Box Box 35)
  - "Hot 'N' Throbbing" actors packet (Box Box 35)
  - production and event calender for "Hot 'N' Throbbing" (Box Box 35)
  - reviews for "Dinah Was" (Box Box 36)
  - Dinah Was Dramaturgy (Box Box 36)
  - "The Royal Family" performance packet (Box Box 36)
  - "The Royal Family", production information (Box Box 36)
  - "A Dolls House", Script 3 VHS videos, 2 Scandinavian cook books (Box Box 37)
  - "A Doll House", 2 scripts (1 English, 1 Swedish) (Box Box 38)
  - "A Doll's House", script with stage cuts, Bio of Ibsen and bound copy of play. (Box Box 38)
  - criticism of Ibsen (Box Box 38)
  - Norway: history and background (Box Box 38)
  - Ibsen: Biographical information (Box Box 38)
  - Norwegian food research (Box Box 38)
  - Ibsen: Theatrical history and information on "A Doll's House" (Box Box 38)
  - research: Norwegian national character and habits (Box Box 38)
  - Norwegian Christmas (Box Box 38)
  - Norwegian art, architecture and furniture (Box Box 38)
  - the Norwegian household (Box Box 38)
  - Norwegian education (Box Box 38)
  - Norwegian geography, climate. and regional information (Box Box 38)
  - Norwegian women (Box Box 38)
  - "A Doll's House": 3 scripts, and interview about Ibsen (Box Box 38)
  - "Tom Walker", playbill and reviews (Box Box 39)
  - "Tom Walker", script and photocopied book, "A Timetable of American History" (Box Box 39)
  - "Coyote Builds North America", by Barry Lopez; script and production information (Box Box 40)
  - "Coyote Builds North America", playbill, stage notes and revisions (Box Box 40)
  - "A Streetcar Named Desire"; script and revisions (Box Box 41)
  - "A Streetcar Named Desire", playbill and script revisions (Box Box 41)
  - "Stand Up-Tragedy"; playbill, reviews, audience reviews (Box Box 42)
  - "A Walk in the Woods"; playbill, reviews, research info (Box Box 42)
  - "A Chorus of Disapproval"; playbills, reviews, research (Box Box 42)
  - "Ring Around the Moon";study guides, research, reviews etc. (Box Box 42)
  - "Ring Around the Moon"; scripts (Box Box 42)
  - "Aix Characters in Search of an Author"; script, reviews, research etc... (Box Box 42)
  - research material, "Norway in a Nutshell" (Box Box 43)
  - research material continued... (Box Box 43)
  - books, 2; "Ibsen" by Harold Clurman and "Henrik Ibsen; Theatre Aesthetic and Dramatic Art" by Jane Ellert Tammany (Box Box 44)
  - "Cat on a Hot Tin Roof"; Playbill, reviews, press release (Box Box 45)
  - playbills for Blue and All My Sons with scripts, reviews, photos, research and production notes (Box Box 45)
  - article,"What is Astrology" (Box Box 45)
  - research on war profiteering (Box Box 45)
  - facts sheet on military (Box Box 45)
  - reviews for "All My Sons" (Box Box 45)
  - research and script for "All My Sons" (Box Box 45)
  - research into World War II era (Box Box 45)
  - "All My Sons", reviews, research, playbill and production notes (Box Box 45)
  - "All My Sons", news articles and interview with Miller (Box Box 45)
  - information on airplane construction (Box Box 45)
  - "All My Sons", info packet (Box Box 45)
  - "All My Sons", notes (Box Box 45)
  - info on Arthur Miller (Box Box 46)
  - AMS Wright Scandal (Box Box 46)
  - "All My Sons" previews (Box Box 46)
  - research into returning vets (Box Box 46)
  - history review of 1947 (Box Box 46)
  - "Miracle Worker"; playbill, reviews and misc. information (Box Box 46)
  - "The Miracle Worker"; production script (Box Box 46)
  - "The Miracle Worker"; visual script (Box Box 46)
  - "The Miracle Worker"; reviews (Box Box 46)
  - "The Miracle Worker"; reviews from the 1950's (Box Box 46)
  - "The Miracle Worker"; actors packet (Box Box 46)
  - "The Miracle Worker"; production paperwork (Box Box 46)
  - "The Miracle Worker"; program hard copy (Box Box 46)
  - "The Miracle Worker"; performance journal (Box Box 46)
  - "The Miracle Worker"; communications and articles (Box Box 46)
  - "The Miracle Worker"; research (Box Box 46)
  - "Blue"; production book (Box Box 47)
  - "Blue"; production book (Box Box 47)
  - "Blue"; script (Box Box 47)
  - "Blue"; script (Box Box 47)
  - "The Great White Hope"; script, research and videos (Box Box 48)
  - "Great White Hope"; production book cont... (Box Box 49)
  - 2 photocopied books on Ida B. Wells-Barnet (Box Box 50)
  - 2 photocopied books on Ida B. Wells-Barnet (Box Box 50)
  - 2 photocopied books on Ida B. Wells-Barnet (Box Box 50)
  - "The Crusade for Justice: The Auto Biography of Ida B. Wells" (Box Box 50)
  - "The Crusade for Justice: The Auto Biography of Ida B. Wells" (Box Box 50)
  - "The Memphis Diary of Ida B. Wells" (Box Box 50)
  - "Constant Star", script (Box Box 51)
  - "Constant Star", script (Box Box 51)
  - "Constant Star", script (Box Box 51)
  - "K-2", actors packets, script and research material (Box Box 52)
  - "Constant Star", script (Box Box 53)
  - "Constant Star", script (Box Box 53)
  - "Constant Star", script (Box Box 53)
  - "The Women", playbill, script, production info (Box Box 54)
  - "The Women", production book (Box Box 54)
  - "Play On", script, playbill, actors packet etc... (Box Box 54)
  - "Tom Walker", script (Box Box 55)
  - "Tom Walker", script (Box Box 55)
  - "Tom Walker", playbill, notes, reviews. misc. materials (Box Box 55)
  - "History of the Theater" (Box Box 55)
  - "The Misanthrope", dramaturgy packet (Box Box 56)
  - "The Misanthrope", script (Box Box 56)
  - "True West", background information and reviews (Box Box 56)
  - "True West", bio of Sam Shepard and notes (Box Box 56)
  - "The Misanthrope", script (Box Box 56)
  - "True West", reviews and background info (Box Box 56)
  - "True West", reviews and articles (Box Box 56)
  - "True West", stories articles and misc. info (Box Box 56)
  - 1995-1996 NEH grant correspondence (Box Box 56)
  - "A Moon for the Misbegotten", dramaturgy source book (Box Box 57)
  - misc. ??? (Box Box 57)
  - "Book of Days", dramaturgy course book (Box Box 57)
  - "Book of Days", dramaturgy course book (Box Box 57)
  - "Book of Days", script (Box Box 57)
  - "Book of Days", script (Box Box 57)
  - "Ma Rainey", research and background info (Box Box 57)
  - "MA Rainey", research and background info (Box Box 57)
  - NEH grant application 1995-1996 (Box Box 57)
  - "The Women", script (Box Box 58)
  - "Great White Hope", production book (Box Box 58)
  - "For the Pleasure of Seeing her Again", playbill, research and background info (Box Box 58)
  - "Book of Days", dramaturgy course book (Box Box 59)
  - "Theophilus North", script (Box Box 59)
  - "Theophilus North", script (2) (Box Box 59)
  - "Theophilus North", script (draft) (Box Box 59)
  - "Theophilus North", script (Box Box 59)
  - "The Misanthrope", script (Box Box 59)
  - Anthems drafts, 2002-2003 season (Box Box 60)
  - anthems drafts 2002-2003 season (Box Box 60)
  - anthems drafts 2002-2003 season (Box Box 60)
  - anthems drafts 2002-2003 season (Box Box 60)
  - "Book of Days", dramaturgy course book (Box Box 60)
  - "An American Daughter", script (Box Box 61)
  - "The Misanthrope", script (Box Box 61)
  - "South Pacific", research (Box Box 61)
  - "South Pacific", research (Box Box 61)
  - "South Pacific", research (Box Box 61)
  - "South Pacific", misc. research (Box Box 62)
  - "South Pacific", pictures (Box Box 62)
  - "South Pacific", ratings and rankings for US Navy / Seabees (Box Box 62)
  - "South Pacific", research for Seabees (US Navy) (Box Box 62)
  - "South Pacific", WWI Nurses (research) (Box Box 62)
  - "South Pacific", recordings (Box Box 62)
  - "South Pacific", letter to Embassy of the Solomon Islands (research) (Box Box 62)
  - "South Pacific", library research (Box Box 62)
  - "South Pacific", research on Rodgers and Hammerstein (Box Box 62)
  - "South Pacific", list of original cast, 1949 (Box Box 62)
  - "South Pacific", research; general WWII information (Box Box 62)
  - "Polk County", actors packet (Box Box 62)
  - "Polk County", actors packet cont. (Box Box 62)
  - "Polk County", actors packet cont. (Box Box 62)
  - ""Life go Boom", by Alonzo Lamonti (preliminary research) (Box Box 63)
  - "Life go Boom", script (final draft) (Box Box 63)
  - "Almost Blue", script and production notes (Box Box 63)
  - "Let 'em Eat Cake", script, music, and misc. notes (Box Box 63)
  - "Let'em Eat Cake", script (2) (Box Box 63)
  - "Hedda Gabler", draft scripts (Box Box 63)
  - "Long Day's Journey into Night", research (Box Box 64)
  - "Long Days Journey into Night", research cont. (Box Box 64)
  - "Long Days Journey into Night", research cont., and study guide (Box Box 64)
  - "Long Days Journey into Night", research cont. (Box Box 64)
  - "Long Days Journey into Night", original script (Box Box 64)
  - "Holiday Heart", research (Box Box 65)
  - "Holiday Heart", research cont. (Box Box 65)
  - "Holiday Heart", research cont. (Box Box 65)
  - "Holiday Heart", research cont. (Box Box 65)
  - "Plough and the Stars", research (Box Box 65)
  - "Plough and the Stars", research (Box Box 65)
  - "Plough and the Stars", research (history, visual, reviews, actors packets) (Box Box 66)
  - "Plough and the Stars", research cont. (Box Box 66)
  - "Plough and the Stars", research and 1st draft script (Box Box 66)
  - "Plough and the Stars", research cont.(text comparison and musical) (Box Box 66)
  - "Plough and the Stars", script (Box Box 66)
  - "I am a Man", production packet (Box Box 67)
  - "I am a Man", computer disks with script (Box Box 67)
  - "I am a Man", script (Box Box 67)
  - "What the Butler Saw", research (The Orton Diaries) (Box Box 67)
  - "What the Butler Saw", research (Box Box 67)
  - "What the Butler Saw", research cont. (Box Box 67)
  - "At the River Stand", video (Box Box 68)
  - "A Month in the Country", cheat sheet (Box Box 68)
  - "A Month in the Country", cheat sheet (Box Box 68)
  - Library Listings and Notes for "A Month in the Country" (Box Box 68)
  - "Turgeneve and Friel", biographical information (Box Box 68)
  - "A Month in the Country", research on Brian Friel (Box Box 68)
  - "A Month in the Country", reviews (Box Box 68)
  - history and time line of Russian History (Box Box 68)
  - "The Russian Intelligentsia" (paper) (Box Box 68)
  - "Moscow" (paper) (Box Box 68)